tcgplayer.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Statement for TCGplayer – TCGplayer.com

**The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Website, why we collect such information, how we may use that information, and whether we disclose that information to anyone.**

At Ascension Gaming Network, Inc. (“AGN”), we value and respect our users and understand your concerns about privacy and security. We will do our best to provide you with a convenient and safe online experience. This Policy applies to our website [www.tcgplayer.com](http://www.tcgplayer.com/) (the “Website”) and constitutes part of our terms and conditions with respect to your use of our Website. By accessing our Website, you acknowledge and agree to be bound by the terms hereof. Periodically, we may update this Privacy Policy and encourage you to check this section for any changes.

### **What personal and other information do we collect and why do we collect it?**

We collect information about you through our Website in an effort to improve your online experience and to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions.

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, which includes name, address, email address, telephone number, and other information that identifies you. We do not require anyone to share any personal information in order to enjoy the Website, which means you can visit the Website without any need to register with us. If you choose to register, we will collect only the personal information that is needed to administer our business, allow you to utilize the full capabilities of the Website, provide superior services to our customers, and communicate information relating to our products and services that we believe to be of interest to our customers.

We may also automatically collect certain information describing your visit, such as your IP address and browser information. We collect information in the aggregate—on an anonymous basis—and may use it to evaluate the ease of use and convenience of our Website and to make further improvements.

We and some of our third party service providers use cookies on our Website. A cookie is a small text file written by an Internet server to a website user's browser where information is exchanged between them, and which is stored on a computer's hard drive to allow us to recognize and track users on our Website to assist us in providing users with a productive online experience. Cookies enable us to store information about your use of our Website such as the areas you visit and the length of your stay. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies and can be reset by using the "Help" portion of the toolbar to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Should you choose to disable any cookies associated with the Website, you will not be able to take full advantage of all the Website's features, but you should be able to navigate the Website without difficulty.

We may also use a third party to help us gather and analyze information about the areas that you visit on the Website to evaluate and improve the customer experience and the convenience of the Website, and to help us evaluate some of the specific information that you provide to us.

In addition to the foregoing, we may also work with business partners that use tracking technologies to deliver advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our Website and your interaction with our communications.

As mentioned above, the information we collect is used to improve our Website, to personalize your online experience, to help us deliver information to you and to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

### **How do we use the information we collect?**

When we collect information from you, we may use it for a number of purposes, including:

  * to complete your purchase transactions
  * to provide the services you request
  * to keep you informed about the status of your orders
  * to identify your preferences, so we can notify you of information or products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
  * to improve merchandise selections, customer service, and overall shopping experience
  * to invite you to participate in customer research
  * to measure the advertising effectiveness of our online and other advertisements and events
  * to respond to your comments and inquiries
  * to communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means
  * to help us understand Website activity and improve your use of our Website

In order for us to maintain the accuracy of your personal information and improve our communication with you, we may also combine the information we collect with other public demographic information.

This Website is not purposefully directed at children under the age of 13. We do not collect or maintain personal information, via the Website or otherwise, from those we actually know are children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13, you should not submit any personal information to us. If you are the parent of a child under 13, please help us protect your child’s privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on this Website or any other without your permission.

### **Who do we share your information with?**

We may pass along information about your shopping cart choices, purchases and preferences to our marketing, customer service or other departments, as appropriate. They may use this information to offer products and services to you consistent with the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy.

Credit card and financing information may be provided to credit card and consumer financing companies as is required to process applications and transactions.

We may also share certain personal information we collect about you with third parties who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use third parties to host our Website, operate certain of its features, send emails, print or send mailings, conduct customer research, authorize and process your payments, manage and analyze data and our advertising effectiveness, and fulfill gift card orders. These third-party service providers are given the information that they need to perform their designated functions and we do not authorize them to use or disclose your personal information for their own or any others' marketing purposes.

On rare occasions we may also be required to disclose your information as is required by law pursuant to lawful requests such as subpoenas, court or agency orders, or as we may reasonably determine to be necessary to protect our rights or the rights of others, to avert harm to persons or property, or to enforce this Privacy Policy.

Your information may also be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfer made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of AGN’s business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in corporate control.

Our Website may also contain links to other sites that are not owned or operated by AGN. These include links to sites hosted by our service providers or partners where, for example, they provide security services or administer promotional programs. Also, links to our Website may be featured on other websites on which we advertise. These links are not intended to be referrals or endorsements of the linked or host sites, and AGN does not warrant, represent or assume any responsibility or liability for the accuracy, security, completeness or operation of any linked site (or any site contained in a linked site) or any host site, or the practices or privacy and other policies contained in any linked site (or any site contained in a linked site) or any host site. We advise you to familiarize yourself, therefore, with the specific legal, privacy and security information contained in any such linked or host sites.

Finally, our Website may contain forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to our customers. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. AGN assumes no liability or responsibility in connection with any customer participation in any of our discussion boards. Without liming the foregoing, AGN assumes no liability for any damages you may suffer because of posts made by or about you. This includes direct, incidental, consequential, indirect, or punitive damages arising out of your access to, or use of, these discussion boards. Without limiting the foregoing, everything on the tcgplayer.com discussion boards are provided to you AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.

### **How do we protect your information?**

We employ various security measures designed to help protect the personal information that we collect from you online. For example, we use Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) encryption technology to protect the security of your credit card and personal information as it is transmitted to us. We have instituted firewalls to help protect our servers and network. Unfortunately, no collection or transmission of information over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any such information.

You can opt out of receiving promotional email from us by indicating that preference when you register with us, by following the “unsubscribe” instructions at the bottom of any emails we may send you, or by calling our customer service line or following the links on our website to remove yourself from our mailing list.

### **Contact us:**

If you have any questions about your privacy or security at our Website, please send an email to our customer service department at: [sales@tcgplayer.com](mailto:sales@tcgplayer.com) and include your name and email address in the message.

### **Changes to this Policy**

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy will be posted here on our Website. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any personal information at our Website, to see if this Privacy Policy has changed. By using our Website, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy. We hope you have a better understanding of the many activities offered on our Website and the ways in which we are committed to safeguarding online privacy. Please do not hesitate to contact us with questions, comments or concerns!
